uh... embargo against channel and this
time
with historical tutorial for perot
uh... or call it a tutorial for more
apart
it in june of this morning for instance
whitefield
but uh...
stations i mean people of
will try to show
style but at least
but that's water over for a firm with a
conclusion about lots of love yours
your base it on uh... on the for five to
ten point lead
uh... there should be brought here
so there is this true
if u
morton purposeful
and uh... i won't follow the this google
over yourself for money acc
training material have been using
uh... the slight differences because the
for what is different
right for the training
but i'm really recommend to two parties
will kill you can actually download it
free of charge
it'd be the reference or if you don't
need to plan for it
you know we don't want to investor
wanted them to go ahead and and all that
will show the link
in summer resort
anyway uh...
that the book is really good and our
report from their homes from
completed
even though it's not really a tutorial
or milk to get these cloning
so that says see what they're going to
use you're going to use uh...
and destroy repro decision it's really
good
in just a bit of a team of the story
world disillusioned
project on children
they're going to use that though you
could actually to use any version of
role for this
but this is makes us so that makes it
easier
so the first thing in reducing the ghost
of our side of
of uh... cadre book provided dot org
you can see it
uh... click on the the download link
your scrawled on a delayed there is the
link to download the latest version of
particles from greek
this includes
bolster the bowl compiler interpreter
and uh...
at the moment of our weather and it
won't be easy for you to school progress
and lots of thing was also a two hundred
commute for uh... development so
recommend to dot on this one
uh... that was also a double click on a
read and follow the instructions just
insulted
i want to sell it to have
um... into start menu
if you go to all programs
strawberry coral and click on the opera
flight you have a good one
uh... which is opening day i_d_
questionable conduct a thorough
empty spaces tried to deliver some text
and what what we're going to do is uh...
go to the following the optional avenue
of the second year in new york and click
on profile script
includes pizza diesel generator daisy
profile script for you
and unexplained depart sleeper
what you want to do is start being
carlos
this is the news standards sing
and then we have to see the because it's
an unsafe armando saving
financial control it
so we save it uh... that's the record it
uh...
wooldridge w let's say
and also say that i can run into role
run script or pressing the f five
bring uh... uh...
being built before being built
and you'll see how the world printers
press any key continue this is says
something between those events
in order to have to let us to see that
throughout the veterans with food
closing meeting
this window and we didn't see that out
pressed some key and and and you're good
controlled
doesn't make a good example to try to
really simple up-close crude but let's
go over these forms
so first line is a school she bang it's
mostly used for unix systems
but it doesn't matter in the form
development of shame
so it doesn't matter
you was at five
book zero zero six this means that
uh... when you're on the screen
uh... if you check first your perot is
at least
platforms it before it was six five
at five point six percent
mouth because this is actually every
nation version before
for the six five point six version
going to use a newer one that we were
going to require a newer one
so i'd changes to fight it
specifically this one and also unable to
view feature single image
but if you can use
district in his warnings there couldn't
be additional
visit the compiler flex
that and made it clear the proloy
interpreter wrote
slightly differently
anymore strictly and
to provide you warnings
in order to evoke awards
several
issues so i would recommend everytime
for every street justice or disease-free
entries
the ship and is not that important for
us
then once you have the
and already what you can see here is
that printed the keyword off parole then
any airstream is going to be between
equality of opportunity to double ports
and uh... backslash n_p_r_
means that
when it's printed out
it should be
printing a new light at the end
as you can see that statement answers a
seven column
uh... because they used the
require a five-day
it already has a new future
to the language doesn't exist earlier so
i can remove the brington instead of
that's right per se
and then i can eliminate those so then
you would
and if represent five now
is all the states to file entrances of
self
you'll see the result of the new version
and the city is the same
it still works
you don't have to drive so much if you
lose five ten and you can hear you say
to you or don't have to have new line
uh... that's fine but it we would like
to have some interaction nisar title
so let's say you that's part of the user
is his name
or at least your
here so we are going to cost a fortune
and then we'll need to agreed to get the
information former user
so i definetly variable period will be
first really help
the school board meeting
are used in my view of the defiant
to declare a variable blore is always
the the prefix of every is still fairly
well
as of this case
the name of the very ably supported him
and damn
used it
discovery tour
preaches reading uh... from the standard
input from the keyboard
area of one ninety of the
user-friendly
process andrew
so the result will go into the symbol of
a variable called
doormen and that they would like to
print it out
so the city carlo
and we explore me
as you can see you can embed if
everyone's into streams and use of the
printed out
that's continue this example
you know that's obvious example
elsewhere
press f five
and ask me about what's my name so i
tried being let's see
press center and they vote on the
telephone
that's great so far
now let's give a bit more polite and
uh... that's our spirit
are you
uh... and uh... let's go along with this
president five a possible and then
still cold food
and a print out to see that ah...
offer four different of in newark
and all the denver co
why is that
then be printed let me tired into their
response from them
we have to president clinton ordered to
tell the
windows and patel oral that input and
but the main that can finish at heading
to dependent variable
and begins removed etc new lives so
we have the new line and sprinted out
uh... even though we don't really see in
this code
and because it's such a special case
for has a special function forty to
remove that scene
by in
which is the function to be moving the
world
from the end of the screen and that
provide the name of the critical
incident removed
training newman from these streak
roaming the streets scripted and
the
obstacles from
but this time as you can see the new
light has gone from here
and it's uh... working fine
i think that's enough for the first
uh...
tutorial
there are some uh... exercise is going
to be
in that
blow fat daddy and the golden's
associated is to set up
screencast
please follow the link below and uh...
you'll find exercises you can
his term and that was you know that